<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
	<title>RSS Title</title>
	<description>This is an example of an RSS feed</description>
	<link>http://www.example.com/</link>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2010 00:01:00 +0000 </lastBuildDate>
	<pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2010 00:01:00 +0000 </pubDate>
 
	<item>
		<title>Everything you missed about the iphone 16, AirPods 4 and the Apple Watch 10</title>
        <link>https://www.cnn.com/2024/09/09/tech/new-iphone-16-apple-release/index.html</link>
		<description> Apple's latest releases include the iPhone 16 with AI features, the AirPods 4 with improved comfort and
        noise cancellation, and the Apple Watch 10 with a larger display and sleep apnea detection.</description>
	  <pubDate>Mon, 9 Sept 2024 19:24:04 +0000 </pubDate>
	</item>

    <item>
		<title>The Electric Vehicle Future is Coming. Just a Little More Slowly</title>
        <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2024/09/05/climate/electric-vehicle-sales-projections.html</link>
		<description> Automakers are slowing down the introduction of new electric vehicle models and adjusting 
        decarbonization goals, but experts say the industry is still on track for an electric future, driven by ongoing investments 
        and the gradual approach to price parity with gas-powered cars.</description>
	  <pubDate>Thurs, 5 Sept 2024 19:39:01 +0000 </pubDate>
	</item>

    <item>
		<title>OpenAI Is Growing Fast and Burning Through Piles of Money</title>
        <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2024/09/27/technology/openai-chatgpt-investors-funding.html</link>
		<description> OpenAI is rapidly growing due to the success of ChatGPT, but is burning through billions in expenses, 
        prompting the company to seek $7 billion in additional funding as it transitions to a for-profit model amidst leadership 
        departures and rising operational costs.</description>
	  <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sept 2024 20:53:49 +0000 </pubDate>
	</item>
    
    <item>
		<title>Meta’s A.I. Assistant Is Fun to Use, but It Can’t Be Trusted</title>
        <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2024/04/24/technology/personaltech/meta-ai-facebook-instagram-chatbot.html</link>
		<description> Meta’s new AI assistant, integrated into apps like Instagram and Messenger, is fun for generating images
         and editing text but struggles with factual accuracy, making it unreliable for tasks like web searches or counting. Despite 
         Mark Zuckerberg’s hope for the chatbot to be the smartest, it struggles with facts, numbers and web search.</description>
	  <pubDate>Wed, 24 April 2024 09:05:38 +0000 </pubDate>
	</item>

    <item>
		<title>When robots can't riddle: What puzzles reveal about the depths of our own minds</title>
        <link>https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20240912-what-riddles-teach-us-about-the-human-mind</link>
		<description>AI struggles with solving riddles and logic puzzles that require abstract reasoning, revealing its limitations
         compared to human thinking, but studying these differences may help improve both AI systems and our understanding 
         of the human mind.</description>
	  <pubDate>Sun, 22 Sept 2024 10:14:28 +0000 </pubDate>
	</item>
</channel>
</rss>

